RG 062:023, Town of Canton
Connecticut State Library
Town of Canton records
1784-1940
Connecticut State Library
Canton (Conn.)
26 cubic feet
Administrative, tax, election, military, land, school vital records for the town of Canton.
RG062_023
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Canton was incorporated in May 1806 and was taken from Simsbury.
Scope and Content
Administrative, tax, election, military, land, school vital records for the town of Canton.
Index Terms
Alternate creator:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Canton)
Subjects:
Elections -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Statistics; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Canton; Soldiers -- Connecticut -- Canton; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Canton; School enrollment -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Statistics; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Canton -- Registers; Deeds -- Connecticut -- Canton; Writs -- Connecticut -- Canton
Places:
Canton (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Canton (Conn.) -- Statistics, Vital
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1784-1940
  - T000480
    - Town meeting records, including warnings, proposals, resolutions, votes, etc., 1885-1910 (Box Box 1)
    - Election returns, 1850-1899 (Box Box 2)
    - Voter lists, 1844-1890 (Box Boxes 3-4)
      See Accesion T000610 for Oversize Box 5.
    - Certificates of electors, 1840-1856 (Box Box 6)
    - Other election-related materials, 1867-1918 (Box Box 6)
    - Town officials' appointments, qualifications, oaths and bonds, 1890-1918 (Box Box 6)
    - Record of military eligibility of male residents, including name, address, birthplace and date, business or occupation, property owner, etc., 1910-1916 (Box Box 7)
    - Military lists, including enrollment lists, 1886-1918 (Box Box 8)
    - Discharges, correspondence, bonus action, etc., 1844-1918 (Box Box 8)
    - Attachments, 1860-1915 (Box Box 9)
    - Deeds, 1784-1899 (Box Box 9)
    - Writs and summonses, 1823-1902 (Box Box 10)
    - Bills and receipts, 1844-1930 (Box Boxes 11-12)
    - Birth, death and marriage certificates, 1878-1904 (Box Box 13)
    - Burial permits, circa 1878-1920 (Box Box 14)
    - School records, including enumerations, 1820-1930 (Box Box 15)
    - Marriage licenses, hunting licenses (stubs), liquor licenses, returns of vital statistics, letters, parental consent to marriages, reports to the state, 1882-1920 (Box Box 16)
    - Dog licenses and dog register, 1882-1920 (Box Box 17)
    - Appointment of jurors, warnings of town meetings, tavern licenses, lists of justices of the peace, financial records, church trustees, certificates of disbursements by candidates for office, 1838-1921 (Box Box 18)
    - Board of relief records, 1838-1940 (Box Box 19)
    - Rate books, grand lists, tax abstracts, 1817-1888 (Box Box 20)
    - Tax Abstracts
      - 1850, 1851, 1852, 1853, 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 21)
      - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865, 1866, 1867, 1868, 1869 (Box Box 22)
      - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1875 (Box Box 23)
      - 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879, 1880, 1881, 1882 (Box Box 24)
      - 1883, 1884, 1885, 1886, 1887 (Box Box 25)
      - 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892, 1893 (Box Box 26)
      - 1894, 1895, 1896, 1897, 1898, 1899 (Box Box 27)
      - 1900, 1901, 1902, 1903, 1904, 1905 (Box Box 28)
      - 1906, 1907, 1908 (Box Box 29)
      - 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913 (Box Box 30)
      - 1914, 1915, 1916 (Box Oversize Box 31)
  - T000610
    - Voter lists, 1900-1930 (Box Oversize Box 5)